$(function() {



const alsaceCards = [
  {
    question: `What would best describe Alsace's growing conditions?`,
    answer: `Varied soil types, dry, and sunny.`
  },

  {
    question: `What is a late harvest wine of Alsace called?`,
    answer: `Vendange Tardive`
  },

  {
    question: `What is 'Selection de Grains Nobles'?`,
    answer: `A late harvest, botrytized, sweet wine.`
  },

  {
    question: `What percentage of the Alsace wine produced is red?`,
    answer: `0-15`
  }
]

const bordeauxCards = [
  {
    question: `Name France's classic appellations for late harvest/ botrytis-affected wines in Bordeaux.`,
    answer: `Sauternes`
  },

  {
    question: `What does 'Gentil' mean?`,
    answer: `A blended wine including a minimum of 50% noble grapes. Superior designation for blends.`
  },

  {
    question: `What is in a typical Médoc blend?`,
    answer: `10%-20% Cabernet Franc, 25%-40% Merlot, 60%-80% Cabernet Sauvignon`
  },

  {
    question: `What are the 3 different quality levels of Bordeaux wine?`,
    answer: `Bordeaux, Region, Region + Chateau`
  },

  {
    question: `What are the 4 red wine regions that stand out in Bordeaux?`,
    answer: `Médoc, Graves/Pessac-Léognan, Pomerol, St-Émilion`
  }
]

const champagneCards = [
  {
    question: `Which 3 grapes can winemakers use to produce Champagne`,
    answer: `Chardonnay, Pinot Meunier, Pinot Noir`
  },

   {
    question: `Name 3 main areas of Champagne`,
    answer: `Marne Valley, Côte des Blancs, Reims Mountain`
  },

   {
    question: `Define dosage`,
    answer: `A mixture of wine and sugar that replaces the wine lost during disgorging.`
  },

  {
    question: `What are the age times for non vintage champagnes`,
    answer: `At least 15 months after bottling`
  },

  {
    question: `What are the age times for vintage champagnes`,
    answer: `At least 3 years after bottling`
  }
]

const italyCards = [
  {
    question: `What is Piedmonts most planted white grape?`,
    answer: `Moscato Bianco - generally for the production of sparkling wines DOCG Astivia Charmat method `
  },

  {
    question: `What is Italy's most important river in Piedmont?`,
    answer: `Po River`
  },

  {
    question: `Name a sparkling red wine form Piedmont (DOCG)`,
    answer: `Brachetto d'Acqui`
  },

  {
    question: `Name a DOCG wine made by metodo classico and the only true rival to the style of Champagne in Italy`,
    answer: `Franciacorta DOCG - chardonnay, pinot nero and a max of 50% pinot bianco are permitted`
  },

  {
    question: `Name all Italian wine classifications`,
    answer: `DOCG, DOC, DOP, IGT, Vino`
  }
]

const loireCards = [
  {
    question: `Name the major sub-regions of the Loire Valley`,
    answer: `Pays Nantars, Anjou-Saumur, Touraine, Central vineyards`
  },

   {
    question: `Define Pouilly-Fumé`,
    answer: `Pouilly-Fumé is 100% sauvignon blanc from the Loire Valley`
  },

   {
    question: `Define Pouilly-Fuissé`,
    answer: `Pouilly-Fuissé is 100% chardonnay from Mâconnais region in Burgundy`
  }
]



})